<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="es">
    <title>Larissa Antunes Amaral - zola</title>
    <subtitle>Projects, Research, Data analysis and more</subtitle>
    <link href="https://larissaamaral.github.io/LarissaAntunesAmaral/tags/zola/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/>
    <link href="https://larissaamaral.github.io/LarissaAntunesAmaral/"/>
    <generator uri="https://www.getzola.org/">Zola</generator>
    <updated>2022-11-01T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>https://larissaamaral.github.io/LarissaAntunesAmaral/tags/zola/atom.xml</id>
    <entry xml:lang="es">
        <title>Refine the search for ELMs progenitors</title>
        <published>2022-11-01T00:00:00-05:00</published>
        <updated>2022-11-01T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
        <author>
          <name>Unknown</name>
        </author>
        <link rel="alternate" href="https://larissaamaral.github.io/LarissaAntunesAmaral/projects/elm-progenitors/" type="text/html"/>
        <id>https://larissaamaral.github.io/LarissaAntunesAmaral/projects/elm-progenitors/</id>
        
        <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;This research project proposes a refined search for ELM progenitors.
Building on the foundational work of Nelemans+01 and exploring the potential role of recently-detached cataclysmic variables (CVs) in ELM progenitor scenarios (Sun &amp;amp; Arras 2018), the study places the investigation of detached ELMs within the broader context of ultracompact binaries, thermonuclear supernovae, and their relevance to LISA signals.
Recent advancements, notably the ZTF survey conducted by El-Badry et al. in 2021, have significantly expanded our knowledge of evolved CV populations, providing a valuable resource for improving the understanding of compact binary systems.
To advance this exploration, the project proposes a refined search for ELM progenitors. This involves a cross-match between Gaia and existing TESS satellite light curves, with the goal of enhancing observational input and contributing to a more comprehensive understanding of the compact binary population.
Motivated by a deep curiosity about the universe&#x27;s intricacies, the project team is committed to leveraging observational techniques and available data to unravel the mysteries behind ELMs, ultimately advancing our understanding of the cosmos.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</summary>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="es">
        <title>Search for new hot DAVs stars</title>
        <published>2019-08-14T00:00:00-05:00</published>
        <updated>2019-08-14T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
        <author>
          <name>Unknown</name>
        </author>
        <link rel="alternate" href="https://larissaamaral.github.io/LarissaAntunesAmaral/projects/ataraxia-zola/" type="text/html"/>
        <id>https://larissaamaral.github.io/LarissaAntunesAmaral/projects/ataraxia-zola/</id>
        
        <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The aim of this project is to search for pulsating white dwarfs with hydrogen atmosphere at
hotter temperatures, i.e. 30 000 K. The pulsation in those stars were proposed by Shibahashi
(2005, 2007) and for the first time observed by Kurtz et al. 2008. Later on, Romero et al.
2020 confirmed the existence of the new pulsating class of hot DA white dwarf stars.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</summary>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="es">
        <title>Evolutionary and asteroseimological study of variable white dwarf stars and its applications</title>
        <published>2016-08-14T00:00:00-05:00</published>
        <updated>2016-08-14T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
        <author>
          <name>Unknown</name>
        </author>
        <link rel="alternate" href="https://larissaamaral.github.io/LarissaAntunesAmaral/projects/asteroseimology/" type="text/html"/>
        <id>https://larissaamaral.github.io/LarissaAntunesAmaral/projects/asteroseimology/</id>
        
        <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The aim of this project was to conduct a study of the evolutionary properties of white dwarf
stars and DA-type pulsating white dwarf stars, called ZZ Ceti, based on a grid of detailed
evolutionary models of these compact objects.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</summary>
        
    </entry>
</feed>
